stockezy.com 2013-09-08

# Stockezy - India's First Social Investing Community.

BSE 19270.06 290.30 1.53%

NSE 5680.40 87.45 1.56%

Fri, Sep 06, 2013 04:00PM IST India Markets Closed.

## Privacy Policy

**stockezy** takes the privacy of its users very seriously. The policy covers how stockezy treats personal information that it collects and receives from its users.

Please read the following very carefully to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the website stockezy.com, and using the services it provides you agree to accept and abide by the practices outlined in the privacy policy.

**Privacy Policy Effective Date: March 22nd, 2008.**  
**Privacy Policy Update Date: January 11th, 2010.**

### Information Sharing, Confidentiality and Security

stockezy collects users personal information such as email address for sign up and registration. The email address is only used to identify the user and send out notifications related to the use of stockezy service. stockezy will never spam you, nor sell, rent or share your personal information. Although we reserve the right to email you occasionally with information such as new feature announcements, website updates and other relevant information to collect your comments to improve our service. 

### Cookies

stockezy may set and access stockezy cookies on your computer. Cookies are a feature of the web browser (Internet Explorer, Mozilla FireFox, etc. ) software that allow web servers to recognize the computer used to access a website. The web browser allows you to prevent accepting new cookies or fully disable cookie function. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser to do so correctly. 

### Advertising

We use the [DoubleClick cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx) on stockezy to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads on this site and other Google and AdSense partner websites. Advertisers may serve ads based on interests associated with non-personally identifiable online activity, such as videos viewed, frequency of uploading or activity on other AdSense partner sites. Advertisers may also serve ads to you based on previous activity on that advertiser's website. This non-personally identifiable information is held separately from your stockezy Account data, or other personally identifying information in our possession. 

You also may choose to [opt out of the DoubleClick cookie](http://optout.doubleclick.com/cgi-bin/optoutgoogle.pl) at any time. If you select the DoubleClick opt-out cookie, ads delivered to your browser by our ad-serving technology will not be served based on the DoubleClick cookie. Find more information here about opting out of the DoubleClick cookie. 

### General

stockezy reserves the right to display third party advertisements on our website. No person under 18 should disclose information on this website without parental consent. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

stockezy reserves the right to change and make modifications to this privacy policy at any time and without notice. We will however notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a notice on our site.
